homeschoolbuyersco-op.org 2007-12-24

# Privacy Policy of the Homeschool Buyers Co-op - Homeschool Buyers Co-op

The Homeschool Buyers Co-op (the "Co-op") will not sell, rent, or otherwise make your personal information available to other people or organizations without your permission, except as may be required by law.

**What Information Is Collected?**  
The term "personally identifiable information" means any information that may be used to identify you, including, but not limited to, your name, address, email address, Internet Protocol address, phone number, billing information, or other contact information. We collect information from you when you join and if you participate in a group purchase that is managed by the Co-op. Below are the specific details on what, where, when, and why this information is collected and how it is used. 

**Registration**  
You provide your name and email address when you join the Co-op. We do not share this information with any third parties. 

**Group Purchases**  
If you have elected to receive special offers from Co-op suppliers, you may receive special time-limited offers to participate in group purchases. Other members will simultaneously receive the same time-limited offer so that, by purchasing as a group, the participating members may receive volume discounts that are not available to members purchasing individually and separately. Should you choose to participate in one of these group purchases, the Co-op will collect and temporarily maintain your order information on your behalf until the time limit for participating expires. At that time, the Co-op will forward your order information to the Supplier whose product you wish to purchase, and destroy any personally identifiable information associated with your order. The Co-op will not retain any record of any such purchases/

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small text files stored by your browser on your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve our website and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize you and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change your browser settings to refuse them. You may change your browser's settings to refuse our cookies. However, if you do so, you may not be able access certain Co-op service. 

**Use of Contractors**  
We may retain the service of outside contractors to perform services on our behalf (for example, to help provide technical support services or deliver new services). At times, we must disclose relevant personally identifiable information about you to our contractors so they may provide these specific services for us. We require our contractors to keep this information confidential and to only use the information on our behalf. 

**Email Communications**  
Periodically, we may send email to you if you have indicated a preference to receive news, updates, special offers, and other information relating to our service. You may unsubscribe from these email subscriptions at the profile web page for your account on our website. 

**Updating Your Information**  
If you desire to change or modify any of the information that you have previously provided to us, you may do so at the Account web page for your account on our website. 

**Children**  
Our service are intended solely for persons 13 years of age and older, or for persons under 13 years of age with parental permission and supervision. If you are under the age of 13 you may not access or use our service except with the permission and supervision of your parents. By using our service you represent and warrant to us that you are 13 years of age or older, or have the permission and supervision of your parents. 

**Links to Third Party Web Sites**  
Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order o understand their privacy and information collection practices. 

**Disclosures Required by Law**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that an applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user. 

**No Error-Free Performance**  
We do not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve our service generally. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it. We will not be liable for any damages, including incidental, consequential, or punitive damages, relating to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
